# Danielle Humilde

# UX/UI Designer

Portfolio d.humilde@outlook.com LinkedIn

#### **SUMMARY**

My passion for design is to create inclusive and diverse interfaces for a wide array of user experiences. I have professional experience in digital marketing and the Design field working contracts and freelancing. I have a certificate in UX/UI Design and Research from OCAD University. With my diverse educational background in Political Science, Digital Marketing and Design, I believe that it widens my perspective for a more holistic understanding of the end user.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### MARSH MCLENNAN Digital Marketing Specialist September 2021 - Current

- Regional Digital Manager for Canada managing Dotcom/DotCA affairs via AEM
- Manage all content being uploaded to the Canadian website (English and French copies); and work closely with the global team to ensure all content is up to brand standards
- · Plan and upload relevant content for campaigns in various industries represented by other marketers on the team
- Design analytic reports via Data Studio of how the Canadian website is performing and identify areas to enhance user experience on the website

#### **BETH MARICIC DESIGN** Digital Design Manager June 2020 - September 2021

- · Managed and create custom webpages to present design concepts for interior design clients
- Developed new marketing assets by redesigning website literature, landing pages, and social media marketing campaigns
- Designed and test different platforms (Instagram, Facebook, YouTube, Spotify) for marketing campaigns to evaluate ROI
  optimisation with strict campaign budget

#### DAVIDS & DELAAT Marketing, Operations & Communications October 2020 - March 2021

- Lead several campaigns and ongoing projects at the firm, such as website enhancement and redesign, TV/radio, billboard, and target/retargeting marketing campaigns
- · Managed and executed owned social media calendar and brand redesign on multiple platforms
- · Studied current real estate market trends to generate relevant content during lull months of real estate to keep audience engaged

## FREELANCE UX/UI Design and Digital Marketing June 2019 - September 2021

- Consulted with various small to mid-sized businesses to review current products and services, to solve user needs and business challenges through Market Research, Campaign Analysis, Visual Design, and Website Architecture
- Businesses ranged from sustainable product brand to defence law firm

# **DESIGN PROJECTS**

## SUBTLE-T App Design Concept

• An app made to help those who are experiencing domestic abuse and need access to resources they need to help them determine a course of action and a safety plan to leave their situation discreetly

## TORONTO TUBE App Design Concept

• An app for Presto card users to adapt contactless payment similar to Apple Pay to enhance app capabilities

## **EDUCATION**

#### OCAD UNIVERSITY UX/UI Design and Research

- Develop UX/UI research skills and design implementation with a focus on User Experience Design and Development
- Micro-certification in Ideation & Prototyping, and Empathy & Social Insight for Human Centric Design

# GEORGE BROWN COLLEGE Post Graduate Digital Media Marketing

 Obtained online certifications for various softwares such as Hootsuite, Brandwatch and Google Analytics for digital media marketing strategies

## UNIVERSITY OF WESTERN ONTARIO BA Political Science

- · Varsity Rowing and Golf
- VP Communications of Political Science Association

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Adobe Experience Manager (AEM) ~ Brandwatch ~ Canva ~ Facebook and Instagram Business Manager ~ Figma ~ Google Ads, Analytics and Data Studio ~ Hootsuite ~ HTML/CSS ~ Human Computer Interaction ~ KV Core ~ Mailchimp ~ Microsoft Office Suite ~ Miro ~ Pardot ~ Prototype Design and Testing ~ Salesforce ~ Squarespace ~ UI/UX Design ~ UX Research ~ Usability Design ~ Web Design ~ Word Press